{
    "subject": "resource/Martin_Foster",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Rotherham",
    "human_readable": "Martin Foster was born in Rotherham.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9276443123817444,
            "question": "Is Martin Foster from Rotherham?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8446972966194153,
            "question": "Where was Martin Foster born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8079291582107544,
            "question": "Who was born in Rotherham?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6610733866691589,
            "question": "In what English town was Martin Foster born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5914453864097595,
            "question": "Can you tell me the birthplace of Martin Foster?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5600743889808655,
            "question": "Rotherham is known as the birthplace of whom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5479172468185425,
            "question": "Where did Martin Foster come from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5245411396026611,
            "question": "What city is associated with Martin Foster's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48227497935295105,
            "question": "To which town does Martin Foster's birth belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29113027453422546,
            "question": "What is the name of the place where Martin Foster originated?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Martin Foster was born in Rotherham.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8237_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which town does Martin Foster's birth belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8237_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city is associated with Martin Foster's birth?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8237_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Martin Foster come from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8237_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8237_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8237_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8237_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8237_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8237_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8237_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8237_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8237_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8237_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8237_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n\"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation: The document with file path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8237/re-ranker-msmarco/63.txt mentions Martin Foster as being born in Rotherham, England."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Martin Foster is from Rotherham, England, and provide his date of birth as October 29, 1977. Therefore, the statement \"Martin Foster was born in Rotherham\" is supported by the information given."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}